<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://www.economist.com/blogs/gametheory</link>
    <description>The politics, economics, science and statistical analysis of the games we play and watch</description>
    <item>
      <title>Parkour’s street stuntmen resent the sport’s new organisers</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/blogs/gametheory/2017/10/guerrilla-gymnastics?fsrc=rss</link>
      <description>A SHIRTLESS man floats through the air, some six or seven stories from the ground. Behind him is the roof of a grubby block of flats. At least five metres (16ft) in front of him and a couple down is another building. Tucked like a diver, he leaps above the abyss, rolls into his landing and sprints away.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 14:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can the marathon’s two-hour barrier be broken?</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/blogs/gametheory/2017/10/runnin-down-dream?fsrc=rss</link>
      <description>IT IS one of running’s three great barriers. The first, a sub-four-minute mile, was achieved in 1954 by Britain’s Sir Roger Bannister, on a gusty day at Oxford University’s dusty cinder track.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 09:26:48 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why fans are riveted by Giancarlo Stanton’s race for seventh place</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/blogs/gametheory/2017/09/baseball-s-most-hallowed-record?fsrc=rss</link>
      <description>THE story of the 2017 Major League Baseball (MLB) season has been the home run. Just three years after a lull in run-scoring sometimes called the “little deadball era”, when offence hit its lowest mark since 1981, equilibrium has been restored almost exclusively on the back of the long ball.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 20:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Cleveland Indians are great, not just lucky</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/blogs/gametheory/2017/09/winning-streaks-baseball?fsrc=rss</link>
      <description>BASEBALL is a sport in which it can be hard to tell the difference between lucky and good.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2017 16:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sorry, Roger: Rafael Nadal is not just the king of clay</title>
      <link>https://www.economist.com/blogs/gametheory/2017/09/draws-tennis?fsrc=rss</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;content-image-full&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2017/09/blogs/game-theory/20170916_woc692.png&#34; height=&#34;967&#34; width=&#34;608&#34;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt; THE RACE is on. Rafael Nadal and Roger Federer, the two men who dominated men’s tennis from 2005-10, have enjoyed a startling resurgence in 2017, splitting the year’s four grand-slam titles.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 20:28:46 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
   
  </channel>
</rss>